{
    "id": "ee334fd3a667405cbf82c80cb0fc7195",
    "title": "Conjunctions Or Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………………. missing the train, I reached on time.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. We use it before an ing form which acts as its object.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "969882f3055149ce9b2e1c686b9297a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… I missed the train, I reached on time.",
            "description": "Though is a conjunction. It is used to introduce a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf28fa5eb1574a638bf995d39e500c86"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked hard ………………………., I failed the test.",
            "description": "However is used to introduce an idea that contrasts with the previous idea.",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf16db17aec3452dbaf58df421d2ca6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she is an atheist, she is a kind hearted woman.",
            "description": "Though and although mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "755ae58e820049e1bf99f5d7a8d32f5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… working two jobs she does not earn enough.",
            "description": "Despite and in spite of are interchangeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Despite of",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "df7e081385224c00a89ca91e3acbf2a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t know anyone at the party ……………………………, that didn’t stop me from having a nice time.",
            "description": "However is used to introduce an idea that contrasts with the previous idea.",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e25b3c2488f84b67b080ce6b80d09ef4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tired …………………………. I was, I went swimming.",
            "description": "As and though can be used in a special structure after an adjective or adverb. In this case, they both mean although.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e06a442ecd7149559d247c93e2b4a1c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "His dad was angry, ……………………………. he had failed his exam.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction because of is a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "767ce601beee446ead50da982db779c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I missed the last bus, ………………………… I had to walk home.",
            "description": "So indicates the result or effect.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d3ec63c2142440e5a4c8da16929d1dca"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he hadn’t applied on time, he could not get the job.",
            "description": "Since is used to introduce the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "Hence",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98d16d1faba64d899f35855600e1b468"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… she is ill, she cannot go to work.",
            "description": "Because indicates the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "So",
                "Therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd401906b38b42c4b975fba0180e1a04"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he could not offer any satisfactory explanation he lost his job.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "521c808c712c4473bd4871a3e88274cd"
        }
    ]
}